haycuoi.com 2012-09-19

# Privacy Policy - Hay Cười - Truyện cười, truyện chế, Hình vui

**Privacy Policy**  
The following webpage outlines haycuoi's collection and use of personal information from it's users. haycuoi.com values the privacy of our members and users, we will never share any personal information of anybody who logs on to haycuoi with anyone. This includes your e-mail address, name, and location. Upon logging on to haycuoi such things as your IP address and hostname are logged for statistical and security reasons. 

**Children's Privacy**  
haycuoi does not knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of 13. We make reasonable efforts to prevent someone who is underage from joining as a member of haycuoi, and will not collect information from them. If haycuoi learns that a child under the age of 13 has become a member, we will close that child's account and delete any information collected about the child. Not withstanding the foregoing, haycuoi may choose to retain some personal information such as the child's e-mail address as a means to prevent the child from re-registering at our website. The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) went into effect in April 2000, and as a result websites all over the world wide web had to change their standards to not collect any information from a child. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.haycuoi.com does not use cookies. 

**Security**  
At haycuoi we make reasonable efforts to protect personal information such as passwords and use technology such as encryption, access control procedures, firewalls, and physical security. We urge you to use a unique password with both letters and numbers to protect your account on haycuoi and it's affiliated websites. If others, including family, friends or other household members access and use the message board through your login credentials, you are responsible for the actions of that individual. Only in extreme cases will your account be fully terminated. 

**Third Parties**  
Third Party websites may collect information from users of haycuoi, this information will include your IP address, hostname, and information about your system to help us serve you better. These are purely used for statistical reasons, and will not be used in any way other then that. Some programs that may collect this information include: eXTReMe Tracking, Google, Nedstat, and Webalizer. 

**Especially Google Adsense Privacy Policy**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

**Website Policy Changes**  
haycuoi reserves the right to change this, and any other policy located on our website at anytime without notifying our users. If you have any comments, questions, or concerns regarding this policy, or any other policy you may send them to us at policy at haycuoi.com.
